import '../utils.dart';

List<QuestionModel> questions = [
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.a,
    options: ['80', '22', '120', '43'],
    question: '100-20',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.b,
    options: ['34', '64', '30', '16'],
    question: 'What is the product of 2 and 32',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.c,
    options: ['IC', 'XI', 'CI', 'IX'],
    question: 'What is the Roman numeral for 101',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.a,
    options: ['6', '3', '2', '5'],
    question: 'Select the odd one',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.b,
    options: ['2', '40', '4', '10'],
    question: 'What is the LCM of 8 and 10',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.c,
    options: ['2/3', '7/3', '8/3', '1/3`'],
    question: 'What is greater',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.a,
    options: ['121', '112', '211', '111'],
    question: '11×11',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.b,
    options: ['3', '6', '0', '5'],
    question: 'Simplify 2+3-5+1×6',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.c,
    options: ['LIX', 'LVI', 'LIV', 'LIX'],
    question: 'What is the Roman numeral for 54',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.a,
    options: ['18', '13', '17', '11'],
    question: 'Select the odd one from the group',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.b,
    options: ['2', '6', '3', '5'],
    question: 'What is the LCM of 2 and 3',
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctOption: Option.c,
    options: ['2', '4', '1', '24'],
    question: 'What is the denominator in 24',
  ),
];
